(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-12T00:53:41.485922",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
輪堂千速生誕祭 2026
Flat Out Summentes
Chihaya Rindo Birthday Festival 2026
重大告知あり
Important Announcement Included
2026.7.8 20:00 START
July 8, 2026, 20:00 Start
輪堂千速生誕祭 Flat Out Summerites 2026 に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to Chihaya Rindo's Birthday Festival, Flat Out Summerites 2026!
盛り上がる準備できてっかー！
Are you ready to pump it up?!
ぶち上げていくぞー！
Let's go all out!
でも、ちょっと今から急いでライブ会場にみんなを連れて行かなきゃなんないから、一緒に行ってくれるか？
But, I have to hurry and take everyone to the live venue now, so will you come along with me?
行くぞー！
Let's go!
熱くなった 銀のメタリックハート
This metallic heart of silver grew hotter
導火線に 火をつけてあげる
I'll light the fuse for you
不思議なほど ハイな気分さ
This is such a wondrous high
砂埃を 巻き上げて行こう
Let's go kick up some dust!
悲鳴をまじらせ 暴走する鼓動
A wild pulse coupled with the screams
目の前には ミサイルの雨
Before my eyes, a rain of missiles
アドレナリン ずっと流して
Adrenaline always pumping
僕の方が オーバーヒートしそう
It'll be me that overheats!
爆発して 灰になっても
Even if I explode and turn into ash
このままだと 笑ってるね きっと
I bet I'll be laughing as I am now
街を追い越して この世の果てまで
Throughout the city, to the ends of the earth
ぶっ飛ばして心中しよう さぁ手を伸ばして！
Let's drive madly and perish together! Come on, reach out!
地平線に 届くように
To reach the horizon,
限界まで 振り切ってくれ
Got to break it down to the limit!
Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
最高のフィナーレを Yeah!
This is the best finale ever! Yeah!
もう数えるくらいで 僕らは消え失せて
Soon enough we'll be no more,
真暗な朝が来るね
and a pitch-black morning will come for us.
お気に入りの服に さぁ着がえたなら
So get in your favorite clothes
駆け出して！
and take off!
あきれるほど 声を上げて
Raise your voice as high as you can,
大気圏を 突破しようぜ
and we'll slip through the atmosphere!
Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
鋼の翼で
With steel wings!
駆けぬけてよ 時間切れまで
Until our time is up, let's keep breaking through,
生まれつきのスピード狂なのさ
'cause I was born speed crazy!
Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
来世でまた会おう Yeah!
See ya in the next world! Yeah!
広い宇宙の 数ある一つ
In a vast universe, one of many
青い地球の 広い世界で
On this blue planet's wide world
小さな恋の 思いは届く
These tiny feelings of love will reach you
小さな島の あなたのもとへ
To you, on this tiny island
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Since I met you, time flows by
思いを込めた 手紙もふえる
The letters filled with my feelings increase too
いつしか二人 互いに響く
Before long, we resonate with each other
時に激しく 時に切なく
Sometimes intensely, sometimes painfully
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Echoing far away, to the distant horizon
やさしい歌は 世界を変える
A gentle song will change the world
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The one who matters most is right by your side
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I only want this to reach you
響け恋の歌
Let this love song ring out
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song ring out
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く
You realize it, and the two of us walk
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
Even on dark paths, the moon shines day by day
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Never letting go of our tightly held hands
思いは強く 永遠誓う
My feelings are strong, I vow eternity
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う
At the edge of eternity, I'll surely say
思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
The same words, with my feelings unchanged
それでも足りず 涙にかわり
Even so, it's not enough, turning into tears
喜びになり 言葉にできず
Becoming joy, unable to be put into words
ただ抱きしめる
I just embrace you
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The one who matters most is right by your side
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I only want this to reach you
響け恋の歌
Let this love song ring out
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song ring out
夢ならば 覚めないで
If this is a dream, don't wake me up
あなたと過ごした時 永遠の
The time spent with you...
星となる
Will become an eternal star
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The one who matters most is right by your side
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I only want this to reach you
響け恋の歌
Let this love song ring out
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The one who matters most is right by your side
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I only want this to reach you
響け恋の歌
Let this love song ring out
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song ring out
はーい！
Hello!
ということで、皆さん！輪堂千速生誕祭2026にお越しくださり、ありがとうございます！
So, everyone! Thank you so much for coming to Rindo Chihaya Birthday Festival 2026!
聞こえていますでしょうかー！
Can you all hear me?!
挨拶します。
Time for my greeting.
エッジドカー、レッツゴー！
Edged car, let's go!
ChromeRunのDJ兼運転手担当、輪堂千速です！
I'm Chihaya Rindo, the DJ and driver of ChromeRun!
こんちはー！
Hello there!
ということで、始まりました！初めての3D生誕祭ライブ！
And with that, my very first 3D Birthday Live has begun!
いっぱい盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's have a ton of fun together!
配信のハッシュタグは、右上...あ、これ、これ...
The hashtag for this stream is in the top right... Oh, wait, this one...
右上のこちらになります。
It's right here in the top right!
ハッシュタグ「#輪堂千速生誕祭2026」になるので
The hashtag is #RindoChihayaBirthdayFest2026
たくさんポストしていただけると、とっても嬉しいです！
So I'd be super happy if you post a lot using it!
ちゃんと見ますからね。
I'll definitely be checking them!
ぜひ、トレンド1位とかになれたりしたら嬉しいななんて思うので
I'd love it if we could make it to the number one trending spot...
いっぱいスクショとかね、貼って、ポストしてください！
So please attach lots of screenshots and post them!
してもらえると、嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you could do that!
わあ、こんちはいいっぱいありがとう！
Wow! Thank you so much for all the "Konchihas"!
ということでね、一旦ちょっと2曲歌わせていただいたので
With that, I've just sung two songs,
振り返っていこうかなと思うんですが
so I'd like to take a look back on them.
まずは1曲目！ドライバーズ・ハイを海沿いを、
First, the first song! Along the coast,
ふぐたろうでドライブしながら歌わせていただきました！どうでしたでしょうか？
I sang "Driver's High" while driving Fugutaro! How was it?
デビューの最初にラルクの曲を歌って、いつかこれも歌ってほしいとたくさん言われていたので
Right after my debut, I sang L'Arc-en-Ciel, and many asked me to sing "Driver's High" someday,
絶対に生誕で歌う！と思って、1曲目に選びました！
so I resolved to sing it today and chose it as the first song!
いや、あの、まあ、あの、あそこカバーの私有地なので
Well, that was a private property for covers,
色々諸々ひっくるめてオッケーです！大丈夫、大丈夫、きっと大丈夫！
so taking everything into account, it's totally okay! It's fine, I'm sure it's fine!
そして2曲目！小さな恋のうたでした！どうでしたか？
And the second song! It was "Chiisana Koi no Uta"! How did you like it?
そう、これ！千早が弾いてましたよ！
Yes, this! Chihaya was actually playing the guitar!
ご存知の方も多いと思いますが、エレキを購入して練習していたんですが、
As many of you might know, I bought an electric guitar and had been practicing,
弾かせていただきました！
and I got to play it live!
エレキで初挑戦するなら「小さな恋のうた」というイメージがあって選んだんですけど、
I felt the first song to challenge on electric should be this one, so I chose it, but...
すんごい難しい！すんごい難しかったんですけど、
It's super hard! It was incredibly difficult, but...
でもね、生誕ライブでカッコいいところ見せたかったので、
I really wanted to show you my cool side at my birthday live,
いっぱい、いっぱい、いっぱい練習して、
so I practiced over and over and over again.
弾けてたよね？なんとか、弾けてたと思います！
I played it okay, right? I think I managed to pull it off!
なのでね、いっぱい後でアーカイブも見直して、聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
So, I'd be happy if you look back at the archives later and listen to it a lot!
そしてお気づきの方もいますが、最初は体育館だったんですけど、外に出てきましたよ！
As some of you noticed, we started in the gym, but now we've come outdoors!
やっぱり夏といえば外！海！山！自然！
After all, summer means outdoors, the ocean, mountains, nature!
そして夏の音楽といえばフェス！をイメージして、
And when it comes to summer music, it's festivals! With that in mind,
夏フェス会場になっております！
we are now at a summer festival venue!
後ろには海もあって、最高のロケーションで、今日はフェスを開催していければなと思っております。
With the ocean in the background, we're in the perfect location to host today's festival.
こんなに広いので、あっちに行ったり、あ、予定にない動きをしてすいません本当に、
It's so spacious! I can go over there—oh, sorry for making such unplanned movements, seriously...
こっちに行ったりしていこうと思っています。
I'm planning to walk around all over the place.
では、次の曲にいこうと思うので、準備のためにギターとマイクを置いてきます。行ってきます。
Now, let's move on to the next song. I'll go set down my guitar and mic to get ready. I'll be right back!
はい、ということで、はい、来ました、来ました。
Alright, I'm back!
ということで、ここからはゲストブロックになりますので、
So from here on, it's time for the guest block!
この後もいっぱい楽しんでいってください！
Please keep having lots of fun!
盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's get pumped!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, not caring how we look
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just believing
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー！
Right here, right now (Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
Right here, right now (Burn!) Slice through and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー！
Right here, right now (Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
険しい修羅の道の中 他人の地図を広げて何処へ行く？
On this steep and treacherous path, whose map are you holding as you go?
極彩色のカラスが それを奪い取って破り捨てた
A rich-colored crow snatched it away and tore it to shreds
さぁ心の目見開いて しかと真実を見極めろ (Yeah!)
Now, open your mind's eye and see the truth of this moment! (Yeah!)
失うモノなんてないさ いざ参ろう！
We have nothing to lose, so let's go!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, not caring how we look
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just believing
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー！
Right here, right now (Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
音を立てず忍び寄る影が いつも僕らを惑わせる
A shadow creeps up without a sound, always trying to lead us astray
有言実行 大きな風が うねりを上げて吹き荒れる
True to our word, a great wind swells and rages wildly
かざした鋭い刀で 己の未来切り開け (Yeah!)
With your sharp blade raised, cut a path to your own tomorrow! (Yeah!)
保証なんてどこにもないさ なぁそうだろ！？
There are no guarantees anywhere, am I right?!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, not caring how we look
Fighting Dreamers
信じるがままに
Just as we believe
oli oli oli oh-! just go my way!
Right here, right now!
ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here, right now!
ぶった斬ってくぜ get the fire!
Slice through it, get the fire!
Right here, right now!
ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here, right now!
ぶった斬ってくぜ get the fire!
Slice through it, get the fire!
We are fighting dreamers
この仲間達と
with these friends of mine
Fighting dreamers
全てを巻き込み
involving everything
Fighting dreamers
志高く
aiming high
oli oli oli oh-!
We are fighting dreamers
高みを目指して
aiming for the top
Fighting dreamers
なりふり構わず
without caring about appearances
Fighting dreamers
信じるがままに
just as we believe
oli oli oli oh-! just go my way!
Go my way! (Don't forget your first impulse ever)
Go my way! (Let's keep your adventurous ever)
(Let's keep your adventurous ever)
Right here, right now!
ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here, right now!
ぶった斬ってくぜ get the fire!
Slice through it, get the fire!
Right here, right now!
ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here, right now!
ぶった斬ってくぜ get the fire!
Slice through it, get the fire!
Burn!
カルマ
[Karma]
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた
A single glass marble was dropped
追いかけてもうひとつ落っこちた
Chasing after it, another fell down
ひとつ分の陽だまりに ひとつだけ残ってる
In a sunny spot made for one, only one remains
心臓が始まった時
When the heart started beating,
嫌でも人は場所を取る
humans took up space, like it or not
奪われない様に 守り続けてる
Continuing to protect it, so it won't be stolen
汚さずに保ってきた手でも
Even the hands I kept clean
汚れて見えた
began to look dirty
記憶を疑う前に 記憶に疑われてる
Before I could doubt my memories, I was doubted by them
必ず僕らは出会うだろう
We will surely meet
同じ鼓動の音を目印にして
Using the sound of the same heartbeat as our guide
ここに居るよ いつだって呼んでるから
I am right here, because I'm always calling out to you
くたびれた理由が 重なって揺れる時
When our worn-out reasons overlap and sway
生まれた意味を知る
We will know the meaning of our birth
存在が続く限り 仕方ないから場所を取る
As long as we exist, we must take up space
ひとつ分の陽だまりに ふたつはちょっと入れない
Two of us can't quite fit in a sunny spot made for one
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた
A single glass marble was dropped
落ちた時 何か弾き出した
When it fell, it pushed something out
奪い取った場所で 光を浴びた
Basking in the light, in the space I seized
数えた足跡など 気付けば数字でしかない
The footprints I counted are now nothing but numbers
知らなきゃいけないことは どうやら1と0の間
What we must know seems to lie between 1 and 0
初めて僕らは出会うだろう
For the first time, we will meet
同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
Using the same flag of screams as our guide
忘れないで いつだって呼んでるから
Don't forget, because I'm always calling out to you
重ねた理由を 二人で埋める時
When the two of us bury our piled-up reasons
約束が交わされる
Our promise is made
鏡なんだ 僕ら互いに
We are mirrors to one another
それぞれのカルマを 映すための
Reflecting our respective karmas
汚れた手と手で 触れ合って
Touching with our dirty hands
形が解る
We feel the shape
ここに居るよ
I am right here
確かに触れるよ
I can certainly touch you
一人分の陽だまりに 僕らは居る
In a sunny spot made for one, we both exist
忘れないで いつだって呼んでるから
Don't forget, because I'm always calling out to you
同じガラス玉の 内側の方から
From inside the very same glass marble
そうさ 必ず 僕らは出会うだろう
Yes, we will surely meet
沈めた理由に 十字架を立てる時
When we erect a cross upon our sunken reasons
約束が果たされる
Our promise will be fulfilled
僕らはひとつになる
We will become one
Woo...
今日も君は
Today too, are you...
信じること
...able to wake up...
忘れずに目覚められていますか？
...without forgetting what you believe in?
時が経つと
As time goes by,
自分さえも
it seems we live in an era...
信じられなくなる時代のようです
...where we can't even believe in ourselves.
自分では気づかないのが
Not noticing it yourself
この症状の特徴で
is the characteristic of this condition,
唯一ある予防法は
and the only way to prevent it...
自分に嘘だけはつかないこと
...is to never lie to yourself!
忘れてたまるもんかよ！！
As if I'd ever forget!
僕がボクじゃなくなったら
If I stop being myself,
たとえ生きてたって 生きてる意味すら見つからんだろ
even if I'm alive, I won't find any meaning in living, right?
声にならない叫びは
This voiceless shout...
僕が声を枯らして
I'll scream it until my throat goes dry!
叫んで歌って
I'll scream and sing!
伝わるまでわめいて
I'll keep crying out until it gets through!
届くまで止めない！！
I't won't stop until it reaches you!
今日も地球は回り続ける
Today too, the Earth keeps spinning.
誰が泣いても怒っても止まらず
It won't stop, no matter who cries or gets angry.
ためしに僕が風邪をひいても
Even if I try getting sick to test it,
もちろん止まることなんてねーわ！！
of course it won't stop!
人生も同じように
Life is just the same,
止まることはなく進む
it keeps moving forward without stopping.
だからそうさ今日も人は
That's why, yes, today too, people...
お手手のシワとシワをあわせんの！
...put their wrinkled hands together!
終わらせちまう事なんか
Putting an end to things...
誰にだってできんだろ？
...is something anyone can do, right?
たとえ終わっちまったって 次のスタートすぐきれんだろ？！
Even if it ends, we can start the next one right away, right?!
今キミが思うキセキも
If you can upgrade the miracle...
底上げさせてしまえば
...that you're thinking of right now,
もうその時点でそのキセキは君にとっちゃ
at that very moment, that miracle will become...
必然のお仲間さ！！
...an inevitable companion to you!
WOW!!
何回ダメダメと言われようが
No matter how many times they say "No, no,"
実際問題そんなん関係なくて
in reality, that doesn't matter at all!
今自分自身必要なものたくわえてそろえとけよ！！
For now, gather and prepare what you need!
なぁそうだろ？！
Hey, isn't that right?!
まだまだ時間はまだあんぞ！！
Not yet, there's still plenty of time!
先見の明 今はとぎすまして
Sharpen your foresight for now,
主人公は一人だけ！！
there is only one protagonist!
自分の物語のはじまり！！
The start of your own story!
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock will soon strike six.
もうそこに一番星
The evening star is already there.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
On the way home, wanting to step on shadows and blend into the night...
どんなに探してみても
No matter how hard I search,
一つしかない星
there's only that one star...
...光年
...light years away...
離れたところから
...shining so bright from far away.
あんなに輝く
Shining so bright.
いいな 君は
Must be nice that you
みんなから愛されて
are loved by everyone.
いいや 僕は
But that's fine, I...
ずっと一人きりさ
will always be on my own.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could be together with you and become a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
A fleeting wish in that starry night...
きらめいて ゆらめいて
Twinkling, shimmering,
震えてるシグナル
quivering with light.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could be together with you and become a constellation,
空見上げて 指を差されるような
I'd gaze up at the heaven and pointed my finger at you.
つないだ線 解かないで
Please, don't break the line that binds us together,
僕がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how dazzling I may be.
まっすぐ時計は8時
The clock points straight to 8 o'clock...
夜空に満天の星
Now the night sky is full of stars.
何億光年 離れたところには
Hundreds of millions of light years away,
もう何かを知らない
we might already not know what's there anymore.
月が綺麗で
Under the beautiful moon,
泣きそうになるのは
I feel like I'm about to cry...
いつの日にか 別れが来るから
Because one day I'll have to say goodbye.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could be together with you and become a constellation,
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
Wandering away like a solitary comet.
消えていく残像は
The fading afterimages...
真夜中のプリズム
...are a midnight prism.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could be together with you and become a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
If only my sincere wish had reached someone.
変われるかな
I wonder if I'll change,
夜の淵を
tracing the edge of the night...
なぞるような
as if sketching it,
こんな僕でも
even for someone like me.
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Beyond the distance, we crossed paths...
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
Because it's karma, we will meet again and again.
雲の隙間で
In the space between the clouds...
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could be together with you and become a constellation,
夜広げて 描こう絵空事
Let's spread the night and paint our fantasy.
暗闇を照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if it's not the full moon that illuminates the darkness.
だから集まって星座になりたい
Because I want to gather and become a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような
Like a colorful light that shines beyond the heaven.
つないだ線 解かないよ
I won't break the line that binds us together,
君がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how dazzling you are.
はい！ ということで！ FGちゃん！
Yes! And with that! FG!
イェーイ！
Yay!
聴いてくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you for listening!
お疲れー！ / お疲れ様でした！
Great job! / Thank you everyone!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
息整えてね
Catch your breath, okay?
あの、FGでね、ずっと
You see, I've always wanted to do a band in FG,
バンドがやりたいと思っていて。で、今日はちょっとエアバンドなんですけれども、
so even though it's just an air band today,
みんなで「星座になれたら」披露させていただきました！
we were so happy to perform "Seiza ni Naretara" for you all!
楽しかったー！ / ありがとう！
That was so much fun! / Thank you!
で、1回自己紹介しとくか？
Well, should we do a quick self-introduction?
オッケー！ / じゃ、りっちゃんから！いつもの順番でお願いします！
Okay! / Starting with Ricchan! In our usual order, please!
はーい！私の歌に、おいで！理央のエンドハウス！
Haaay! Come join my song! Rio's End House!
Flow Glowの、べ、べ、ベース担当、響咲理央なのだ！
Flow Glow's b-b-bass player, Hibasaki Rio here!
イェーイ！低い声かっこいい！
Yeah! Your deep voice is so cool!
ちよちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！ / ありがとうー！
Chihaya-chan, happy birthday! / Thank you!
にこたんが来た！Flow Glowの...
Niko-tan has arrived! Flow Glow's...
何だっけ？キーボード、キーボード担当、にこたんだよ！
What was it? Keyboard, keyboard player, Niko-tan here!
ありがとうー！ / そして？
Thank you! / And next?
はーい！ぴちぴちの120点足りてる、Flow Glowの... ドラム担当！
Hiya! The lively, 120% filled up Flow Glow's... drum player!
枢です！ちよ、お誕生日おめでとう！
I'm Su! Chihaya, happy birthday!
ありがとうー！ / そして？あ、はい！
Thank you! / And next? Ah, yes!
せーの、うるびー！
One, two, Uruby!
いつもキラキラな キラキラビビです！
I'm always sparkling, Sparkling Vivi!
あ、忘れてた！ビビはギター担当！
Oh, I forgot! Vivi is in charge of guitar!
ドゥルルルル... 足引っ張ってるよ
*strum* / You're holding us back!
ちは お誕生日おめでとう！
Chihaya, happy birthday!
ありがとう！ 嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
いや、ということでみんな来てくれてありがとう！
Well, with that, thank you everyone for coming!
え、なんかいいお知らせがあるんじゃないの？
Wait, isn't there some good news?
あ、なんと！トレンド1位になったらしい！
Oh, actually, apparently we reached number 1 on trending!
やったー！ すごい！ 嬉しい！
Yay! Awesome! I'm so happy!
なんか、今まではね、ちはやって2文字だから、トレンドに乗らねえのよ。
Like, up until now, "Chihaya" is short, so it didn't get on trending.
だから、なんか、乗ったらいいなと思ってたんだけど、こんな誕生日に嬉しいプレゼントをいただきまして、本当にありがとうございました。
So, I was hoping it would trend, but getting such a wonderful present on my birthday, thank you so much.
いっぱいツイートしてくれた！ ありがとう！ もっとツイートしてね！
Everyone tweeted so much! Thank you! Please tweet even more!
はい、ということで、生演奏披露しましたけど、皆さんどうでしたか？
Alright, with that, we performed live music, but how was it, everyone?
楽しかった！ 楽しかった！
It was fun! It was fun!
ドラムも叩きたくなりました
It made me want to play the drums too.
ドラム経験者なんだよね
You have experience playing the drums, right?
そうなんです、実は
That's right, actually.
だから、いつか、FGバンドをね...
So, someday, an FG band...
絶対できる！できる！
We can definitely do it! We can!
結成したいよね。今回は、エアバンドだったので、にこたんにね、キーボードを担当していただいたんですけど...
We want to form one. This time, since it was an air band, we had Nico-tan play the keyboard...
ねえ、すごかったでしょ？
Hey, wasn't I amazing?
すごかった！ 本当に凄かった
You were amazing! You really were.
手で弾いてたもんね。すごい、全身で弾いてくれてた
You were playing with your hands after all. Amazing, you were playing with your whole body.
一歩も触れずにね！ 確かに！
Without even touching it once! Indeed!
イェーイ！
Yay!
でも、めっちゃみんな楽しそうに...ちはもすごい楽しかったし、みんなも楽しそうにしてくれてとっても嬉しかったです。いつか実現させましょう！
But everyone looked so fun... Chihaya had a blast too, and I was so happy everyone enjoyed it. Let's make it a reality someday!
したい！したい！ やろう！
We want to! Let's do it!
そん時はみんな、今回の楽器でいいんですか？
At that time, is everyone fine with using the same instruments as this time?
あ、えっ？
Ah, wait...
違うのがやりたいって！
Someone wants to do something else!
歌、歌う！ ダメダメ！
I'll sing! No, no!
ケンカ、ケンカだ
It's a fight, a fight!
にこたんはさ、やるとしたら何の楽器やりたい？
Nico-tan, if you were to play, what instrument would you want to play?
何でもいいよ。もう出まくってるよね、もうね。 ギター？今、ギター、ギター、ドラム、ベースがあるんだけど。
Anything is fine. They're all taken, right? Guitar? Right now we have guitar, guitar, drums, and bass.
そしたら、やっぱり、キーボードしかないよね
In that case, the only thing left is keyboard, after all.
バイオリンいける！バイオリン！ これがあるじゃん！
You can do violin! Violin! There's this one!
いや、ちょっと違う気がする... バイオリン入ってるバンド、めっちゃかっこいいよ！
No, I feel like that's a bit different... A band with a violin is super cool!
打楽器はどう？トライアングルとか
How about percussion? Like a triangle.
トライアングル... ビビはトライアングルね
Triangle... Vivi gets the triangle.
全員でなんか打楽器バンド？
How about a percussion band with everyone?
それもいいね
That's good too.
全然違うタイプのやるからやめてそれ
Stop that, we'll end up doing something completely different.
そういうのもやってみたい、楽しそう。
I'd want to try that too, sounds fun.
FGの企画とかでやったりするのね
Maybe we can do it as an FG project.
確かに！ やろうやろう
Totally! Let's do it, let's do it.
ということでね、今回はFGちゃんたちに来ていただきまして、本当に今日はね、長い時間リハーサルから付き合ってもらって、本当にありがとう！
So, with that, we had the FG girls come over today. Thank you so much for joining me for such a long time, starting from rehearsals!
おめでとう！ ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
このお礼は、ちはが何でもします券を皆様に贈呈いたします。
As thanks, I present to you all a "Chihaya will do anything" coupon.
え！何でも？
What! Anything?
ひとり1枚？ ひとり1枚！やったー！
One for each of us? One for each of us! Yay!
取り消し、取り消し！ 取り消し券なし！
Cancel, cancel! No cancellation coupon!
美味しいご飯ごちそうさま！
Treat us to delicious food!
それはもちろん、全員に奢らせていただきます！
Of course, I'll treat everyone to that!
よかった、よかった！ 今日もお弁当豪華だったしね
Great, great! The bento boxes today were luxurious too.
お弁当、奮発しました。よかったです、喜んでいただいて。
I splurged on the bento boxes. I'm glad you liked them.
まだあるので持って帰ってください。 はーい！
There's still more, so please take them home. Okay!
ではね、そろそろ次の曲に行きたいと思います！
Now then, I think it's about time we move on to the next song!
みんなも見届けてくれるかな？ バッチリ見るよ！
Will everyone watch over us? We'll definitely watch!
では、ライブ見てくれているみんなもまだまだ盛り上がっていってくださいね！
So, everyone watching the live stream, keep on getting hyped up!
イェーイ！
Yay!
コメント欄は「なんでも」って言ってる。 なんでも？
The comment section is saying "anything". Anything?
すぐ帰ろうとしないで！
Don't try to go home so quickly!
リスナーさんたちには何でもしないですけど、FGちゃんたちには何でもしたい気持ちでいますよ。
I won't do "anything" for the listeners, but for the FG girls, I feel like doing anything.
やったー！気持ちだけじゃなくてね！
Yay! Not just in feelings, right!
やばいやばい！みんな！ありがとうございました！
Oh no, oh no! Everyone! Thank you so much!
俺も一緒に行こう。シュシュシュ...
I'll go along too. *swoosh swoosh*
打上花火
[Song: Uchiage Hanabi - Lyrics & Composition: Kenshi Yonezu]
あの日の見渡した渚を
The beach we looked out on that day...
今も思い出すんだ
...I still remember it even now.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words engraved on the sand...
君の後ろ姿
...and your silhouette from behind.
寄り添う波が
The close waves...
足元をよぎり何かをさらう
...drift past our feet, washing something away.
夕凪の中
In the evening's calm...
日暮れだけが通り過ぎて行く
...only the twilight passes us by.
パッと光って咲いた 花火を見ていた
We watched the fireworks light up and bloom.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely, this summer isn't over yet.
曖昧な心を 解かして繋いだ
Unraveling and connecting our uncertain hearts,
この夜が続いてほしかった
I wished for this night to last forever.
「あと何回君と同じ花火を見られるかな」って
"I wonder how many more times I can see the fireworks with you..."
笑う顔に何ができるだろうか
What can I do for that smiling face of yours?
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと 繰り返す波と情動
Hurting, rejoicing—emotions loop like ebbing waves.
焦燥 最終列車の音
Impatience, and the sound of the last train.
何度も言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
I'll put it into words again and again to call your name.
波間を選び もう一度
I'll choose the waves and try once more...
もう二度と悲しまずに済むように
...so that we never have to feel sad again.
ハッと息を飲めば 消えちゃいそうな光が
A light that seemed ready to fade with a gasp...
きっとまだ胸に住んでいた
...was surely still living in our hearts.
手を伸ばせば触れた あったかい未来は
The warm future we could touch by reaching out...
密かに二人を見ていた
...had secretly been watching us.
パッと花火が
With a flash, the fireworks...
...the fireworks...
夜に咲いた
...bloomed in the night.
夜に咲いて
Blooming in the night...
...blooming in the night...
静かに消えた
...and quietly faded away.
...quietly faded away.
離さないで
Don't let go.
離れないで
Don't leave me.
もうすこしだけ
Just a little longer...
...just a little longer...
このままで
...stay just like this.
あの日見渡した渚を 今も思い出すんだ
I still remember the shore we looked out over that day.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉 君のうしろ姿
The words engraved in the sand, your silhouette.
パッと光って咲いた 花火を見ていた
We watched the fireworks light up and bloom.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely, this summer isn't over yet.
曖昧な心を 解かして繋いだ
Unraveling and connecting our uncertain hearts,
この夜が続いてほしかった
I wished for this night to last forever.
ららら...
Lalala...
ソラニン
[Title: Solanin]
思い違いは 空のかなた
Our misunderstandings are far beyond the sky.
さよならだけの 人生か
Is life just made of goodbyes?
ほんの少しの 未来は
Even though I saw a tiny piece of the future...
見えたのに
...clearly in sight.
...えたのに
...even though I could see it.
さよならなんだ
It's goodbye after all.
昔住んでた小さな部屋は
The small room I used to live in
今は誰かが住んでんだ
is occupied by someone else now.
君に言われたひどい言葉も
The cruel words you said to me,
無駄な気がした毎日も
and the days that felt meaningless too...
あの時こうしていれば
If only I had done things differently back then.
あの日に戻れれば
If only I could return to that day.
あの頃の僕にはもう
But to who I was in those days,
戻れないよ
I can no longer go back.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
For example, if a gentle kind of happiness
だらっと続いたとする
had simply dragged on lazily,
きっと悪い種が
surely some bad seed
芽を出して
would sprout,
もう
and it would already...
さよならなんだ
...be goodbye after all.
寒い冬の冷えた缶コーヒー
A cold can of coffee in the freezing winter,
虹色の長いマフラー
and a long rainbow-colored scarf.
小走りで路地裏を抜けて
Jogging lightly through the back alleys,
思い出してみる
I try to remember.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
For example, if a gentle kind of happiness
だらっと続いたとする
had simply dragged on lazily,
きっと悪い種が
surely some bad seed
芽を出して
would sprout,
もう
and it would already...
さよならなんだ
...be goodbye after all.
なんだ
After all...
さよなら
Goodbye...
それもいいさ
...that's fine too.
どこかで元気でやれよ
Be well somewhere out there.
さよなら
Goodbye...
僕もどうにかやるさ
...I'll manage somehow too.
さよなら
Goodbye...
そうするよ
...yeah, I will.
はい！
Yes!
はい、ということで！
Alright, so!
『ソラニン』をお送りいたしました！
I just performed "Solanin"!
いかがだったでしょうか？
How was it?
いや、あの...
Well, you see...
見覚えのある方もいらっしゃるのでは
I'm sure some of you might recognize this,
ないでしょうか？
right?
これ、まあ、あの、初めて見る方もいらっしゃるかなと思うんですが、
Well, some of you might be seeing this for the first time,
あの、FGの3Dお披露目のときにも、
but back during FG's 3D debut showcase,
えっと、ギターの弾き語りをお披露目させていただいたんですけれども、
I performed an acoustic guitar cover then too,
そのときよりもレベルアップできていたでしょうか？
but do you think I've improved since then?
初めて、多分、最初の頃に練習したのが『ソラニン』で、
Probably the very first song I ever practiced was "Solanin",
そこからずっと、ちゃんとできた姿をみんなに見せたかったので、
and since then, I've always wanted to show everyone a proper performance,
この曲を選びました。
so that's why I chose this song.
そしてですね、ギター、ちはの音だけじゃなくて、
Also, besides my own guitar,
もう一本ソロとかベースがあったと思うんですが、
there was another guitar solo and bass line, right?
それはですね、ちはのギターの先生に一緒に弾いていただきました！
Well, my guitar teacher actually played those parts with me!
なんかレッスンのときにセッションしてたら、
When we were jamming during one of our lessons,
「え、めっちゃかっこよくね？」ってなって、
we realized, "Whoa, this sounds awesome!"
「先生もよかったら一緒に弾いてくれませんか？」って言って、
So I asked, "Would you like to play along with me?"
一緒にね、弾いていただきました。
And they were kind enough to play together with me.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
つわはちでゴー！
Tsuwahachi, let's go!
ファイティン・ドリーマーしました。
I performed "Fighting Dreamer".
どうですか？やっぱり1曲目はぶち上げていきたいなと思って、
How was it? I wanted to start off with a bang,
つわはちですごい盛り上がる曲を選びました。
so I chose a really hype song by Tsuwahachi.
もう先輩たちのぶち上げがカッコよくて、ちほも頑張るぞってなったので、
My seniors' hype was so cool, it made me want to do my best too,
楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
so I hope you enjoyed it.
そして、2曲目はトワ様と「カルマ」を歌いました。
And for the second song, I sang "Karma" with Towa-sama.
やっぱりトワ様の低音が大好きなので、
I really love Towa-sama's low voice,
ちょっと無理を言って原曲キーでね、
so I asked a bit too much of her and we sang in the original key.
すごい低い中、一緒に歌っていただきました。
She sang with me in that very low range.
トワ様ありがとうございました。めっちゃかっこよかったです。
Towa-sama, thank you so much! It was incredibly cool.
そして、3曲目がルイ先輩と「自分ROCK」。
And the third song was "Jibun ROCK" with Lui-senpai.
いや、かっこよすぎない？やっぱりルイ先輩かっこよすぎない？
I mean, wasn't that way too cool? Lui-senpai is just too cool, right?
ヤバいんですけど。
It's insane.
あの、本当にルイ先輩のね、カッコいい、ちょっとこう、がなりの効いた、エッジの効いた声で
I really wanted to sing this song with Lui-senpai's cool, slightly raspy, edgy voice,
歌いたいなと思ってこの曲を選びました。超かっこよかったよね。
so I chose it. It was super cool, wasn't it?
そして、6曲目が「星座になれたら」。さっきね、フブちゃんたちと一緒にワイワイした「星座になれたら」で、
Then the sixth song was "Seiza ni Naretara". The one we all hyped up earlier with Fubu-chan and the others,
7曲目、
and for the seventh song...
激エモの、にゃんちゃん、おかゆ先輩との「打上花火」。
The super emotional "Uchiage Hanabi" with Nyan-chan and Okayu-senpai.
どうでしたか？もうマジで、
How was it? Seriously,
本当に、おにぎり、あの、皆さんには申し訳ないんですけれども、
to all the Onigiri (Okayu's fans), I am so sorry,
あの瞬間はちょっとジニンおかゆ先輩の彼氏のつもりでもう、
but for that moment, I pretended to be Okayu-senpai's boyfriend,
ってやってしまいました。
and did... that.
もう最高でした。ありがとうございました、本当に。お返しします。ありがとうございました。
It was the best. Thank you so much, really. I'll return her to you. Thank you.
というね、エモエモな、かっこいいからエモまでのパートがありました。楽しんでいただけてますか？
So, that was the cool to emotional part of the show. Are you all enjoying it?
ちょっとコメント見てみようかな。
Let's take a look at the comments.
「エモすぎた」「泣いた」。わかる、わかる、めっちゃエモいよね！
"It was too emotional", "I cried". I know, I know! It was so emotional, right?
千速もなんか、やりながら「エモすぎるこれ！」と思って、やってましたよ！
Even I was thinking "This is too emotional!" while performing.
ありがとう。めっちゃ良かったよね。
Thank you. It was really great, wasn't it?
さあ、ということでね、ちょっとね、千速ね、喋らせると、
All right, so, if you let me talk,
喋りすぎてしまうので、ちょっと次のパートに行きたいんですが、
I'll talk way too much, so I'd like to move on to the next part.
ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
From here on, we have some exciting announcements!
輪堂千速 誕生記念2026 グッズ販売の告知となります！
Announcements for Rindo Chihaya Birthday Celebration 2026 Merchandise!
生誕グッズが出るぞ！こちらをご覧ください。ドン！
Birthday merch is coming! Take a look at this. Ta-da!
はい！盛りだくさんですね！
Yes! There's so much stuff!
イラストはトリダモノ先生、まーまに描いていただきました！ありがとうございます。
The illustration was drawn by Toridamono-sensei! Thank you so much.
ギターをね、弾いてるライブのワンシーンをイメージして描いていただきました。
She drew it with the image of a live scene playing the guitar.
いや、めっちゃかっこいいよね。
Wow, it looks incredibly cool, doesn't it?
それではね、詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちら！
Now, let's look at the details. First up, this!
「Chihaya BD Fes Tシャツ 2026」でございます！
The "Chihaya BD Fes T-shirt 2026"!
キービジュアルのイラスト全身を使用した、かっこかわいいTシャツです。
A cool and cute T-shirt featuring the full-body key visual illustration.
バンドTシャツっぽくしたくて、ちょっとロゴとかいかつい感じにしてもらったので、
I wanted it to look like a band T-shirt, so I asked for the logo to look a bit edgy,
ぜひぜひライブ、ライブとか日常でも着てもらえたら嬉しいです。続いては、こちら！
so I hope you'll wear it to concerts or even in your daily life. Next is this!
「ピックケースキーホルダー」です！
The "Pick Case Key Holder"!
お気に入りのピックを入れて、おしゃれに持ち運べるキーホルダーです。
A key holder that lets you carry your favorite picks in style.
キーホルダーがメインで、3枚のピックは付属品として付いています。
The key holder is the main item, and three picks are included.
ピックケースホルダーにはピックが1枚入る仕様です。
The pick case holder is designed to hold one pick.
あの、今回のために描いたサインとか、ロゴとか、
It comes with a set of picks featuring a special signature, logo,
あとは「Flatout」っていうロゴ。今回のね、タイトルにもなってる「Flatout」のロゴが描かれてるピックがセットになっています。
and the "Flatout" logo, which is the title of this live. They are included in the set.
続いては、こちら！
Next up, this!
「ちはとお出かけバッグ」です！
The "Outing Bag with Chiha"!
前にポーチが付いていて、
It has a pouch on the front,
前のポーチをひっくり返すと、中身を見せて「推しバッグ」にチェンジできる、
and if you flip the front pouch, you can show the inside and change it into an "Oshi bag",
ちょっとね、機能性のあるバッグ。斜めがけのバッグになっています。
which makes it a very functional crossbody bag.
色んなところ、これで、お出かけしてください。そして続いては、こちら！
Please go out to various places with this. And next up, this!
「どこでもふぐ太郎ティッシュカバー」！
The "Anywhere Fugutaro Tissue Cover"!
ふんわりとした質感の、ふぐ太郎モチーフのティッシュカバーです。
A tissue cover with a soft texture, designed in the motif of Fugutaro.
え、かわいいよね！お家でも、車でも、職場でも、ふぐ太郎を連れていけます！
It's so cute, right? You can take Fugutaro with you at home, in your car, or at work!
そして続いては、こちら！
And next, this!
「シチュエーションボイス」です！
The "Situation Voice"!
タイトルは「ライブリハーサルボイス」。
The title is "Live Rehearsal Voice".
ライブ前のリハーサルで、ドキドキ、緊張してる千速のシチュエーションボイスになっておりますので、
It features Chihaya feeling nervous and excited during the rehearsal before the live show,
ドキドキの緊張感をね、ぜひ聞きに来てください。そして、フルセット購入特典もあります。こちら！
so please listen to my nervous excitement. And we also have full set purchase bonuses. Here!
「直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入り チェキ風ブロマイドカード」です！
A "Cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten signature and foil-stamped printed message"!
全部ね、直筆で、千速がサインを書きますのでね、
Chihaya will write all of the signatures by hand,
ぜひぜひフルセットで購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです。
so I'd be very happy if you bought the set.
そして、特典ボイス。タイトルは「ライブ後、君と」になります。
Also, the bonus voice. The title is "After the Live, with You".
先ほどのボイスと合わせて聞くと、またよりエモさを感じられるのではないかなと思うので、
If you listen to it together with the previous voice, it might feel even more emotional,
ぜひこちらも聞いてみてください。改めて、フルセットはこちらになります！
so please check this out too. Once again, the full set is right here!
やっぱね、これ全部、Tシャツ着て、バッグ持って、キーホルダーつけて、ふぐ太郎持って、
If you wear the T-shirt, carry the bag, attach the key holder, and bring Fugutaro,
どこでも行ける「千速セット」。千速セットなので、
you'll have the "Go-anywhere Chihaya Set". Since it's the Chihaya set,
まあ買うならフルセットの方がいいよね！
if you're going to buy, the full set is definitely better!
21時、この後21時カートオープンとなりますので、数量限定ではないので、
The cart opens at 21:00 tonight. It's not limited in quantity,
ぜひね、ゆっくり購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします。
so I'd appreciate it if you took your time to make a purchase. Thank you so much!
お願いします！
Please check it out!
そして皆様待望の、お知らせがございます！
And now, I have an announcement you've all been waiting for!
こちら！
Look at this!
なんと、輪堂千緋世、ソロとして初めてのオリ曲「Flatout」が、
Believe it or not, Chihaya Rindo's first-ever solo original song, "Flatout"...
このあと24時、7月9日木曜日の0時、
...will be released digitally after this at midnight! That's 12:00 AM on Thursday, July 9th.
このあとね、3時間ちょい後くらいからデジタルリリースされます！
That's in just over three hours from now!
やったー！
Yay!
今回のライブのタイトルにもなっている「Flatout」は、オリ曲のタイトルでございました！
"Flatout," which is also the title of this live stream, was actually the title of my original song!
えー、この配信が終わった後にMVが公開されますので、そちらもぜひお楽しみに！
The music video will be released right after this stream ends, so please look forward to that as well!
概要欄にね、のちのち多分リンクが貼られたり貼られなかったりすると思うのでそちらもチェックしてみてください。
I think the link will eventually be added to the description, so please check that too.
新曲、このあとやっぱ早速聴きたいですよね！
I'm sure you all want to hear the new song right away!
このあと披露するので絶対に聴いてください。
I'll be performing it right after this, so make sure to listen to it!
最後まで、最後までね、チャンネルはそのままで、見ていってくださいね。
Please stay tuned until the very end without changing the channel!
以上、輪堂千緋世生誕祭2026のグッズ情報と、リリース情報でした！
And that's all for the merchandise and release announcements for Chihaya Rindo's Birthday Festival 2026!
みんな買ってね、サブスクでも聴いてね！
Everyone, please buy it and listen on streaming services too!
はい！
Alright!
ということで、怒涛のお知らせコーナーでした。ここからいよいよライブもクライマックスです。でも、まだまだあります！
And that wraps up our whirlwind announcement corner. From here, the live show finally heads into the climax. But we're not done yet!
盛り上がる準備できてますか？最後一緒にぶち上げていこうね！
Are you ready to get hyped? Let's go crazy together at the end!
では、準備してきます。そのチャンネルはそのままで。
Well then, I'm going to get ready. Stay tuned on this channel!
I wanna fly so high Yeah, I know my wings are dried
「翼仰げば」って人は云う
"Raise your wings," people say
その向こうにあるは無情
But it's only heartless beyond
飛べる者 落ちる者
Ones who fly, ones who fall
誰も見てない
People pay no attention
気にも留めない
They don't care at all
それでも飛び続けた
But I kept on flying
傷ついた言葉乗せ
Just wanted to put the hurt
運ぶたいから
And bring them away
追いかけて届くよう
Chase, we'll make it there
僕等一心に羽ばたいて
Forcing our wings to flutter
いつかまた会う日まで
Until the day we meet again someday...
Shiny Smily Story (2022 ver.)
[Song: Shiny Smily Story (2022 ver.)]
はい、ということで、輪堂千速生誕祭、ここまで見てくれたみんな、本当にありがとうございました！
Alright, so, thank you all so much for watching the Rindo Chihaya Birthday Festival up to this point!
えー、次が、本当にラストの曲です。
Next up is truly the last song.
えー、この曲は、いつか、みんなと、現地で会って、
I'd love to sing this song at the very end...
ライブができた時に、最後に歌えたらいいなって、そんな思いで、
...whenever we can meet in person and hold a live concert.
千速のいろんな気持ちを込めて作ってもらった曲です。
It's a song created with so many of Chihaya's feelings poured into it.
千速の、初めてのオリ曲、聴いてください。『Flat out』
Please listen to Chihaya's first original song, "Flat out".
メランコリーのリフレイン 午前3時
A melancholy refrain at 3:00 AM.
夢を見るには少し遅すぎた Midnight
Midnight, a bit too late to be dreaming.
言葉にならないままの想いが
My thoughts, remaining unspoken...
溢れだしてしまう前に
...before they start overflowing...
飛び出した部屋 光を見たくて
I ran out of my room, wanting to see the light.
“どうせ”だって 何度だって 諦めようとしたって
Even when I tried to give up over and over, saying "What's the use?"
“だけど”きっと 今日もそっと 伸ばした手 あの星まで
But surely, today as well, I quietly reach my hand out to that star.
自分さえだませない 嘘はもうやめて
Stop telling lies that can't even deceive yourself.
踏み込め
Step on the gas!
駆け抜けて
Run through!
音も風も抜き去って
Outstripping both sound and wind,
迷いさえも振り切って
shaking off even my hesitation,
スピードを上げて
accelerate!
行かなくちゃ
I must go,
夜のまだその向こうへ
beyond the night,
見たこともない世界へ
to a world I've never seen before.
今 最高速度で
At maximum speed right now,
高鳴る方へ
towards where my heart beats fast!
答えなんてなくたって ただこうしていたいだけ
Even without an answer, I just want to be like this.
未完成で不完全な道の先まで 行けると信じて
Believing I can make it to the end of this incomplete, imperfect road.
差し障りないように生きた日々
Days lived safely to avoid any trouble,
諦めの言い訳を探すのをやめて
stop searching for excuses to give up.
もどかしい気持ち 窓の向こうに
This frustrating feeling beyond the window...
輝くあの星みたいに ああ なりたかったんだ
Oh, how I wanted to be like that shining star.
足りない物だらけだって
Even if I'm full of flaws,
どれだけ離されたって
and no matter how far behind I'm left,
止まればそこまでなんだ
if I stop, that's where it ends.
進め
Keep moving forward!
未来を変える瞬間は
The moment to change the future...
いつかじゃなくて今なんだ
...is not "someday", it's right now!
進め
Keep moving forward!
先へ さあ
Go on, ahead!
もっと遠くまで
Even further away,
確かめに行くんだ Flat out
I'm going to find out, flat out!
駆け抜けて 夢に見たその舞台へ
Run through to the stage of my dreams,
決して振り返らないで
never looking back.
スピードを上げて
Speed up!
行かなくちゃ
I must go,
夜のまだその向こうへ
beyond the night,
見たこともない世界へ
to a world I've never seen before.
今最高速度で
At maximum speed right now,
信じる方へ
towards what I believe in!
答えなんてなくたって ただこうして 走り出したんだ
Even without an answer, I just started running like this.
止まらないよ
I won't stop.
さあ あの星に届け
Now, reach that star!
輪堂千速生誕祭2026、見ていただいて本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for watching the Rindo Chihaya Birthday Festival 2026!
これからも、みんなと向こうの景色、たくさん見に行きたいです。
From now on, I want to see so many more sights together with all of you.
これからも千速のことを好きでいて、ついてきてくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be so happy if you keep loving Chihaya and follow me on this journey.
本当に今日はありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for today!
ありがとうね！
Thank you!
輪堂千夜生誕LIVE
[Rindo Chihaya Birthday LIVE]
お越しいただきありがとうございます
Thank you so much for coming.
初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？
How was my first live show??
見てくれたキミのおかげで初めての2.0完成します
Thanks to you watching, my first 2.0 update is complete.
いつかキミの声が直接きけるその時まで
Until the day I can hear your voice in person...
これからも走り続けるよ！！！
I will keep on running forward!!!
今日は本当にありがとう
Thank you so much for today.